<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Barin Chiropractic</title>
    <link>https://barinchiro.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Barin Chiropractic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://barinchiro.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Professional Chiropractic Services</title>
      <link>https://barinchiro.com/sections/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barinchiro.com/sections/first/</guid>
      <description>At Barin Chiropractic it is our goal to provide professional Chiropractic Services. Whether you have been in an automobile accident, hurt on the job, suffering from health problems or just feeling the effects of life’s everyday stress, our office is designed to meet your needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Dr. Barin</title>
      <link>https://barinchiro.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barinchiro.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Vladimir Barin, DC Dr. Vladimir Barin completed his undergraduate studies at the University of Physical Education in Moscow, Russia, where he received a BA. He attended Palmer College of Chiropractic West in San Jose, CA, obtaining his doctorate in 2001. Dr. Barin is licensed in Massachusetts and is National Board certified. He also undergoes postgraduate training in the rehabilitation of whiplash injuries, headaches, neck, and back pain.&#xA;Before opening his private practice in 2007, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our areas of expertise</title>
      <link>https://barinchiro.com/sections/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barinchiro.com/sections/second/</guid>
      <description>Neck Pain Back Pain Sciatica Tennis Elbow Shoulder Pain Knee Pain Ankle Pain Headache Injured in a car accident or at work?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://barinchiro.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barinchiro.com/services/</guid>
      <description>Safe and Effective Chiropractic Care At Barin Chiropractic, we focus on delivering safe and effective chiropractic care to relieve your pain naturally, without the use of drugs or surgical procedures. By combining gentle chiropractic adjustments, targeted muscle therapy, and physical therapy modalities, we restore your body’s natural balance, creating an optimal environment for healing.&#xA;What Causes Pain Pain can arise from a variety of factors, including improper lifting techniques, poor posture, accidents, falls, and stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We adjust to your schedule</title>
      <link>https://barinchiro.com/sections/call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barinchiro.com/sections/call/</guid>
      <description>If you are currently hurting in the areas mentioned above, call my office now at 617-782-5100&#xA;Flexible hours. weekend and evening appointments available. Please call to schedule an appointment.&#xA;Our practice accepts most major insurance plans.&#xA;We value your privacy: read more about our privacy policy here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our office</title>
      <link>https://barinchiro.com/office/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://barinchiro.com/office/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Vladimir Barin&amp;rsquo;s office is located at 35 Highland Circle Suite 303, Needham, MA, 02494 Corner of Highland Circle and Oak Street&#xA;Public Transportation: Bus: 59 Needham St. @ Oak St. Flexible Hours. Weekend and Evening appointments available. Make an appointment now 617-782-5100 </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
